[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Dead Sea is actually a lake.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many years ago did the formation of the Earth take place?", "correct_answer": "4.6 billion years", "incorrect_answers": ["14.6 billion years", "46 billion years", "4.6 trillion years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Happiness is fleeting in the story of Bambi as another stag fights him for this mate. What is this deers name?", "correct_answer": "Ronno", "incorrect_answers": ["The Stag", "Mulet", "The Would-Be  Prince"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On March 19 2008 President Bushs approval rates  were 31% and 69%. What were his chances of winning the 2008 presidential race?", "correct_answer": "0%", "incorrect_answers": ["31%", "50%", "69%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What caused the Air India Flight 182 crash on June 23, 1985, when 329 people passed away?", "correct_answer": "Bomb explosion on board", "incorrect_answers": ["Miscalculation of the altitude", "One of the pilots had a heart attack", "Engine malfunction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What poet noted for his realistic depictions of rural life received four Pulitzer Prizes?", "correct_answer": "Robert Frost", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Kelly", "Robert Browning", "Robert L. Hass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Sean Connery voice in the 1993 animated movie The Thief and the Cobbler?", "correct_answer": "Tack the Cobbler", "incorrect_answers": ["Zigzag the Grand Vizier", "King Nod", "The Thief"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Police officers who use slimjims to assist locked out motorists have been killed by airbags.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following albums are by the band Red Hot Chili Peppers. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "In Another Land", "incorrect_answers": ["Blood Sugar Sex Magik", "Freaky Styley", "By the Way"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the title of a 1996 Tom DiCillo film starring John Turturro.", "correct_answer": "Box of Moonlight", "incorrect_answers": ["Sun, Moon and Stars", "Lunar Landings", "Box of Moonbeams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Isabella Bird the first woman to climb Longs Peak, the highest point in Rocky Mountain National Park?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A yellow ribbon is worn to recognize the struggle that men and women face when battling cancer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]